He announced that, by a special decree of Comrade Napoleon, Beasts of England
had been abolished.
From now onwards, it was forbidden to sing it.
The animals were taken aback.
>> Why?
cried Muriel.
>> It is no longer needed, comrade.
Beasts of England was the song of the rebellion, but the rebellion is now
completed. The execution of the traitors this afternoon was the final act. The
enemy, both external and internal has been defeated. In Beasts of England, we
expressed our longing for a better society in days to come, but that
society has now been established.
Clearly, this song has no longer any purpose.
Frightened though they were, some of the animals might possibly have protested,
but at this moment, the sheep set up their usual bleating of Four legs good, two legs bad.
Which went on for several minutes and put an end to the discussion.
So, Beasts of England was heard no more.
In its place, Minimus, the poet, had composed another song which began Animal Farm, Animal Farm,
never through me shalt thou come to